A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers' Files, Executive and Program Officers' Files FA1831
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers' Files, Executive and Program Officers' Files
1952-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
Heginbotham, Stanley
Rockwell, Richard
Sills, David
Szanton, David
Pearson, Robert
Kessel, Frank
Bronson, Susan
FA1831
12.72 Cubic Feet 34 boxes (33 letter document containers and 1 half letter document container)
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in three series:
1. Vice President, 1973-1995
2. Program Staff, 1977-1989
3. Executive Associates, 1952-1991
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to RAC in 2016 and 2017 by the SSRC and ingested by RAC as Accessions 2016:005, 2016:010, 2016:074, 2016:076, 2017:021, and 2017:024.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains SSRC committee proposals and planning documents, correspondence, meeting files, SSRC publications, and research reports of:
Stanley Heginbotham, Vice President from 1990-1995
Richard Rockwell, Program Officer from 1977-1991
Robert Pearson Files, Program Officer, files from 1987-1990
Frank Kessel, Program Director for the Culture, Health and Human Development Program, files from 1987-1990
Susan Bronson, Progam Associate, later Program Director, for the Program on the Former Soviet Union from 1991-1997
David Sills, Executive Associate from 1973-1988
David Szanton, Executive Associate from 1975-1991
- Vice President, 1973-1995; 1; 5.51 Cubic Feet 14 letter document box and 1 half-letter document box
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains files of SSRC Vice President Stanley Heginbotham, who served in the role from 1990-1995.
  - Stanley Heginbotham's Files, 1973-1995; 1
    Stanley Heginbotham served as Vice President of the SSRC from 1990-1995. Stanley Heginbotham's files contain proposals for the SSRC's Comparative and Transnational Seed Grant Competition, meeting materials, financial reports, budget files, and correspondence. The subseries also holds material created by David Featherman who served president of the SSRC from 1989-1995.
    - International Studies Project - Task Force Planning, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - Staff Meeting Discussion on Mission-Oriented Basic Research and the Policy Context, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - SSRC Native American American Studies Advisory Panel - Contact List, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Presidential Search, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 173)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2035
    - Comparative and Transnational Advisory Panel Members, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7-8, Box 2, Folder 9-12)
      Berry, Sara
      Cummings, Bruce
      Iriye, Akira
      Mason, Karen
      Sewell, William, Jr.
      Yanagisako, Sylvia
    - Comparative and Transnational Advisory Panel Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Announcements, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Comparative and Transnational Competition - Proposal Acknowledgments, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Comparative and Transnational Competition - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Muslim Societies, C-11, Central and Inner Asia, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Africa, C-12, Generating Comparable Social and Economic Databases in Sub-Saharan Africa (Becker, Charles), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Western Europe, C-13, European Identity and its Conceptual Roots (Hall, Peter A.), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - South Asia, C-14, Realm of the Domestic Under Imperialism (Greenough, Paul), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Korea, C-15, Writers in Action (Kim, Uchang), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Near and Middle East, C-16, Social and Political History of Innovation (Hess, Andrew C.), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Near and Middle East, C-17, Questions of Modernity Strategies for Post-Orientalist Scholarship on South Asia and the Middle East (Mitchell, Timothy), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - Korea, C-18, State, Law, and Family Among Late Industrializers (Sorensen, Clark), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Proposal - South Asia, C-19, Nationalizing the Past (Greenough, P.), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Requests for Proposals, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Announcements, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Comparative and Transnational Competition General Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - International Studies Project, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - International Studies Project - Review Phase, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Fellowships and Grants Offered in 1991-1992 Brochure (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - The Future of International Studies in American Higher Education, Blue Ribbon Panel, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Interim Research Planning Start-up Grant Announcements, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Interim Research Planning Start-up Grant Competition Correspondence and Memos, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Japan, I-1 Legal Change and Political Economy in East Asia, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - I-2, Southeast Asian Literature Project (Hutterer, Karl), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Soviet Studies, I-3, Reconstructing "Russian" History: Culture and Empire (Burbank, Jane), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - South Asia, I-4, South Asian Humanities Project, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Latin America, I-5, Economic Liberalization and Consolidation of Political Democracies in Latin American (Stallings, Barbara), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Western Europe, I-6, A New Europe: Rethinking Constructs of Collective Behavior (Hall, Peter), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Africa, I-7, The World the Diaspora Makes, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Proposal - Near and Middle East, I-8, Bridging the Divide (Migdal; Keeler), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Interim Start-up Grant Request for Proposals (Final and Drafts), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 44-45)
    - International Studies Project - Working Group on Collaborative Relations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - International Studies Project - General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - International Studies Project - Long-term Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - International Studies Project - Short-term Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - International Studies Project - Program Training, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Africa Program, C-1, Development and Social Science, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Southeast Asia, C-2, Politics of the Tangible Past (Hutterer, Karl), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - C-3, Global Economic Reform (Wilson III, Ernest J.), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - C-4, Convention and Contention in Collective Action Research (Tarrow, Sidney), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Japanese Studies, C-5, Indigenous Narrative Tradition and Modern Historiography (Vlastos, Stephen), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Grant Competition - Correspondence and Memos, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Southeast Asia, C-6, Re-imagining National Communities, (Rosaldo, Renato), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Global Environmental Change, C-7, Comparative Examination of Landed Property Rights (Richards, John F.), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Latin America, C-8, Environmentalism of the Poor, (Stallings), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - Latin America, C-9, New International Context of Development (Stallings), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Comparative and Transnational Seed-Money Grant Proposal - South Asia, C-10, Politics of Late Transformation (Kohli, A.), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP), 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 62-63)
    - From Soviet Studies to Eurasian Studies Draft, Report Prepared for the Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP), undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) Meeting at American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1991 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Transnational Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 66-68)
    - Ford Grant - Program for International Studies Historical Materials, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 69-70)
    - Cuba Initiative, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Comparative Study of Muslim Societies - Core Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Comparative Study of Muslim Societies, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 73-76)
      Proposal - The Popular Appeal of Islam in the 1990s
      Meeting with Ford
      General Committee Business
    - Formation of a Joint Committee on East Asia - Working Files of Japan and Korea Committees, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Staff Consultative Group and the Subcommittee on Program Assistant Concerns, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 78-79)
    - Historical Data on Foreign Area Dissertation Grants, 1973-1991 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1990 August-1994 September (Box 9, Folder 81-83, Box 10, Folder 84-87, Box 11, Folder 88-90, Box 12, Folder 91-92, Box 13, Folder 93-94, Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Chronological Correspondence File, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 172)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2061
- Program Staff, 1977-1995; 2; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
  This series contains the the files of:
  Richard Rockwell, Program Officer from 1977-1991
  Robert Pearson Files, Program Officer, files from 1987-1990
  Frank Kessel, Program Director for the Culture, Health and Human Development Program, files from 1987-1990
  Susan Bronson, Program Associate, later Program Director, for the Program on the Former Soviet Union from 1991-1997
  - Richard Rockwell's Files, 1977-1989; 1
    Richard Rockwell was an SSRC Program Officer from 1977-1991. This subseries contains meeting materials, reports related to Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP), Institute of Peace and Security Studies (IPSS) correspondence and grant files, and Richard Rockwell's correspondence files.
    - Meeting on Employment, Productivity and the Unrecorded Economy, 1981 May 1 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - The Survey of Income and Program Participation - An Interim Assessment, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for a Study on Subjective Social Indicators, 1979 March 1 (Box 14, Folder 98)
      National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council, Assembly of Behavioral and Social Sciences Committee on National Statistics
    - Agenda - Assembly of Behavioral and Social Sciences Committee on National Statistics - Panel on Survey-Based Measures of Subjective Phenomena, 1980 March 21-22 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Individuals and Families in Transition: Understanding Change Through Longitudinal Data, Papers Presented at the SSRC Conference in Annapolis, Maryland, 1988 March 16-18 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - Final Report: Feasibility Study of Long-Term Access to Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP) Volume I, 1987 July 31 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Final Report: Feasibility Study of Long-Term Access to Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP) Executive Summary, 1987 July 31 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Final Report: Feasibility Study of Long-Term Access to Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP) Volume II - Technical Appendices, 1987 July 31 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Panel on Survey-based Measures of Subjective Phenomena Committee on National Statistics, 1980 January 18-19 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Proposal Submitted to Division of Social Sciences National Science Foundation by Social Science Research Council, 1977 June 1 (Box 16, Folder 105-106)
    - Institute of Peace and Security Studies (IPSS) Chronological Files, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 107-108, Box 17, Folder 109-110, Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Institute of Peace and Security Studies (IPSS) Development Grants, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Richard Rockwell Chronological Files, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 113, Box 19, Folder 114-116, Box 20, Folder 117-118)
  - Robert Pearson's Correspondence, 1987-1990; 2
    Richard Pearson was an SSRC Program Officer. The correspondence in this series spans from 1987-1990.
    - Chronological Files A-Z, 1987-1990 (Box 28, Folder 174-177, Box 29, Folder 178-182)
  - Frank Kessel's Files, 1988-1993; 3
    Frank Kessel served as SSRC Program Director for the Culture, Health and Human Development Program, files from 1987-1990. The subseries contains files related to conference planning, life course research, research reports, and psychology.
    - Dr. Mamphela Ramphele Visit, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 183)
    - South Africa Correspondence, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 184)
    - Children, Research, and Policy: Towards a Multi-disciplinary Consortium of Child Research Meeting, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 185)
    - Veena Das Colloquium - The Phenomenology of Everyday Violence, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 186)
    - SSRC Retreat Memos, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 187)
    - Cambridge Meeting - Agenda for 8/28-29 Meeting, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 188)
    - Cambridge Meeting - Premeeting July 24th, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 189)
    - Cambridge Meeting - Frank Kessel Correspondence, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 190)
    - Health, Culture, and Society - Palo Alto Conference Logistics, etc., 1991 (Box 30, Folder 191)
    - William T. Grant Foundation Psychology Staff, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 192)
    - Frank Kessel Invoice Memo, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 193)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Health, Culture, & Society General, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 194)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Health, Culture, & Society Conference Memos to Participants Invitations, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 195)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Health, Culture, & Society - Reponses to Memos II, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 196)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Featherman, LeVine, Klienman et al, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 197)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Memo to Participants, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 198)
    - Post Cambridge Meeting - Committee Meeting II Memos, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 199)
    - The SSRC and Psychological Studies: A Seminar on Possible Futures - Participants Memo, 1992 March (Box 31, Folder 200)
    - SSRC and Psychology Meeting - Attendance Questionnaire, 1992 March (Box 31, Folder 201)
    - SSRC and Psychology Invite Letter, 1992 January (Box 31, Folder 202)
    - SSRC and Psychology Publications Memo, 1992 March (Box 31, Folder 203)
    - SSRC and Psychology Hotel and Food, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 204)
    - 1991 Intra-Office Memos (Box 31, Folder 205)
    - Committee on Culture, Health and Society, 1990-1992 (Box 31, Folder 206)
    - Fernando Mendoza Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 207)
    - William Dressler Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 208)
    - Diana Slaughter-Dafoe Articles, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 209)
    - Children, Research, and Policy: Towards a Multi-disciplinary Consortium of Child Researchers Materials, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 210)
    - Abandoned Ambitions: Transition to Adulthood in the Life Course of Working-Class Boys, Gerald Handel, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 211)
    - MIDMAC/NYC Get-Together Memo, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 212)
    - Successful Mid-Life Development: Personal Well-Being and Social Productivity in the Middle Years, O. G. Brim, 1989 March 1 (Box 32, Folder 213)
    - MIDMAC - Articles and Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 214)
    - MIDMAC - Caribbean Immigrants Interview Transcripts, Mary Waters, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 215)
    - MIDMAC 1992-1993 - Weisner Article, Family Lifestyles and School Achievement (Box 32, Folder 216)
    - MIDMAC 1992-1993 - Nadine Marks Memo on Longitudinal Surveys (Box 32, Folder 217)
    - MIDMAC 1992-1993 - Reading Material for Meeting, 1992 October 14 (Box 33, Folder 218)
    - Annual Report for 1990, MacArthur Foundation Research Network on Successful Mid-Life Development, Gilbert Brim, Director (Box 33, Folder 219)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation Research Network on Successful Midlife Development, Gilbert Brim, Proposal for Activities During Phase II, January 1, 1992-December 31, 1994, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 220)
  - Susan Bronson's Files, 1989-1995; 4
    Susan Bronson was Program Associate, and later Director, for the Program on the Former Soviet Union at the Social Science Research Council from 1991-1997. The subseries primarily contains files related to the review process of the international program at the SSRC.
    - International Programs - Core Funding and Budget Planning, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 221)
    - National Security Education Program - Memos, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 222)
    - Professional Staff Issues Group, 1989-1992 (Box 33, Folder 223)
    - International Program Review, 1991-1995 (Box 33, Folder 224-226, Box 34, Folder 227-230)
    - International Program Review Memos, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 231)
    - AERA (American Educational Research Association) Spencer Panel - Challenging the Prevailing Academic Culture, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 232)
- Executive Associates, 1952-1991; 3; 2.85 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes and 1 half-letter document box
  This series contains files of SSRC executive associates David Sills and David Szanton.
  David Szanton was an executive associate at the Social Science Research Council from 1975-1991.
  David Sills was an executive associate at the Social Science Research Council from 1973-1988. In 1988, he retired with emeritus status.
  - David Sills' Files, 1952-1987; 1
    The subseries contains the files of David Sills, executive associate at the Social Science Research Council from 1973-1988. In 1988, he retired with emeritus status. The subseries includes meeting materials, publications, reports, copies of SSRC bylaws, and memos.
    - Research Opportunities in China for American Humanists and Social Scientists, Edited by Kenneth Prewitt, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 119)
    - Advisory Panel on International Educational Exchange, Final Report, 1986 February 26 (Box 20, Folder 120)
    - Collective Resources for the Support of Social Science Research, Kenneth Prewitt, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 121)
      Reprinted from Social Science Research Council Annual Report, 1984-1985
    - Security Studies and the Social Sciences, Kenneth Prewitt, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 122)
      Reprinted from Social Science Research Council Annual Report 1983-1984
    - Report of the Acting President, Francis X. Sutton, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 123)
      Reprinted from Social Science Research Council Annual Report, 1985-1986
    - Directory of Foreign Area Fellows, 1952-1972 (Box 21, Folder 124)
      Directory of Foreign Area Fellows of the Joint Committee on The Foreign Area Fellowship Program of the American Council of Learned Societies and SSRC, 1962-1972, Formerly administered by The Ford Foundation, 1951-1962, Compiled and Edited by Dorothy Soderland, Assistant Editor Leslie Wendell
    - Working Group on International Relations - Meetings and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 125-126)
    - Chinese Graduate Study Delegation Dinner (Princeton Club), 1980 September 19 (Box 21, Folder 127)
    - American Sociological Association (ASA) Site Visit, 1979 November 16 (Box 21, Folder 128)
    - Committee on Problems and Policy - Minutes, 1979 March 23 (Box 21, Folder 129)
    - Working Group on the History of Congress, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 130)
    - Memos - David L. Sills to Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 131)
    - Meetings, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 132)
    - UNESCO, 1975-1980 (Box 22, Folder 133-134)
    - National Science Foundation Reorganization Meeting at SSRC, 1980 September 12 (Box 22, Folder 135)
    - Copy of Hanover Conference 1926 Meeting Minutes, undated (Box 22, Folder 136)
    - Proposals, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 137)
    - Notes on Foundations (Brief Sketches), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 138)
    - Fundraising - Proposal - Carnegie Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 139)
    - New Council Ideas - "Exciting Ideas", 1976-1986 (Box 23, Folder 140)
    - Fundraising, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 141)
    - SSRC Bylaws - 2nd Revision, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - SSRC Bylaws - 3rd Revision (Gender-Specific), 1978 (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - SSRC Bylaws - 4th Revision, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 144)
    - SSRC Bylaws - Original and Revision #1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 145)
    - SSRC Bylaws - Revision, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 146)
    - Nominating Committee, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 147-148)
    - Board of Directors Transition/Search, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 149)
    - Symposium on Individual and Social Change (June Board Meeting), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 150-151)
    - Memos - David L. Sills to Kenneth Prewitt, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - Committee on the Composition of the Board, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 153)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 154)
    - Elbridge Sibley's History of the Social Science Research Council, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 155)
    - Nature Review, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 156)
    - Review of Hans Zeisel's Say It With Figures, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 157)
    - Bernard Berelson Article for World Biographies, 1985 September (Box 24, Folder 158)
    - David L. Sills - Filing System, 1979 July (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - David L. Szanton's Correspondence, 1982-1991; 2
    This subseries contains David Szanton's general correspondence and correspondence related to Area Studies and Southeast Asia. Szanton was an Executive Associate at the Social Science Research Council from 1975-1991. More correspondence can be found in Social Science Research Council records, Near and Middle East, Record Group 3, Series 9; Series 2: Joint Committee on the Comparative Study of Muslim Societies, 1984-1995. The files are David Szanton Chronological Correspondence Files A-Z from 1988-1990.
    - David L. Szanton Correspondence, 1982-1991 (Box 24, Folder 160-162, Box 25, Folder 163-166, Box 26, Folder 167-169)
      Arrangement
      Arranged alphabetically
    - Southeast Asia Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 26, Folder 170)
    - Area Studies Panel Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 171)